fnbr.co 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy | fnbr.co — Fortnite Cosmetics

## Privacy Policy

fnbr.co respects user privacy and aims to be transparent with the small amount of data we collect.

This document sets out to explain what information might be collected when using our site.

#### Personal Information

We limit the amount of information we collect to a minimum. When using the site, your IP Address, browser type/version and referring website are logged for diagnostic purposes and are deleted within 48 hours of being stored. This information is not shared externally and is only accessed when necessary to maintain site stability.

If you decide to vote on the shop page, we will temporarily store your IP Address for a short period to prevent spam and abuse.

If you would like us to delete any information stored about you, please contact us using the email listed at the bottom of this page with the subject “GDPR” and information to verify yourself. To prevent further logging, do not continue to use this site.

#### User Accounts

Logging into our website requires authorisation through either Twitter or Discord. This does **not** give us access to private information such as Direct Messages.

We store the username and ID for the platform you authenticated with (Twitter or Discord) and keep track of your votes/comments on item pages to aid spam prevention and to provide features such as reminders.

If you have API access, we also store when you last used your API key, when it was last changed and the key itself. Allowing us to limit or revoke access if necessary, to prevent abuse.

We also keep track of the language you have chosen to use via the language picker built into the site. This is stored as a cookie and, if logged in, sent to our servers to be saved to your user account for continuity at future logins.

#### Third Party Advertising

We also use third party advertisements on fnbr.co to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, the browser you used to visit.

We use NitroPay as our advertising provider, you can view their privacy policy [here](https://nitropay.com/privacy).

General information about third-party use of cookies for advertising or to opt-out of these can be found at [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/) and [youradchoices.com](http://youradchoices.com/).

#### Cookies

We don’t use cookies directly unless you are logged in with an account or using a different language.

Third party services used to operate the site may use cookies, these are listed below:

  * [Cloudflare](https://cloudflare.com/) — [Cookie Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/cookie-policy/) and [Security & Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/)
  * [Google Analytics](https://google.com/analytics) and [AdSense](https://google.com/adsense) — [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), [Advertising Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) and [Google Partner Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

You can opt-out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

We recommend you read the policies listed above to understand what they mean. Cookies can be blocked through your browser settings, however, in some cases this may prevent access to the site (commonly determined by Cloudflare who use cookies for security).

#### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we do, a clear notice will be made available on the site to ensure you are aware of any revisions.

This policy was last updated on February 9th 2019.

#### Contact Us

You can email us at [contact@fnbr.co](mailto:contact@fnbr.co).
